<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="first_headline">Brokerages Expect Yahoo! Inc. (YHOO) to Post $0.99 Earnings Per Share</string>
    <string name="first_story">Yahoo! logo Analysts expect Yahoo! Inc. (NASDAQ:YHOO) to report earnings of $0.99 per share for the current fiscal quarter, Zacks Investment Research Reports</string>
    <string name="second_headline">The Chart Is Speaking Loud and Clear For Yahoo! Inc. (YHOO)</string>
    <string name="second_story">Yahoo! Inc.(YHOO) has been having a set of eventful trading activity and it is clear from an examination of the charts that traders are now fully aware of the companys key metrics</string>
    <string name="third_headline">Yahoo! Inc. Posted gains of 1.43% in the Last Trade</string>
    <string name="third_story">Currently, the market capitalization of Yahoo! Inc (YHOO) is 45.66 Billion. YHOO has a 1-year high price of $47.88 and 1-year low price of $35.05</string>
    <string name="fourth_headline">Yahoo! Inc.(YHOO) Is Trying To Tell Investors Something Through Its Technicals</string>
    <string name="fourth_story">The technicals for Yahoo! Inc(YHOO) has spoken via its technical chart and the message is loud and clear. Based on that message, this is the relevant information necessary to make sense of that current setup.</string>
    <string name="fifth_headline">Yahoo! Inc.(YHOO) Taking the Oath in June: Credit Suisse</string>
    <string name="fifth_story">Yahoo! Inc.(NASDAQ:YHOO) reported 1Q17 results with better-than-expected net revenues; Search revenue beat was partially offset by shortfalls in both Display and Other Revenue.</string>
    <string name="sixth_headline">Yahoo Back At January 2015 Levels After Q1 Beat</string>
    <string name="sixth_story">Yahoo Inc. (NASDAQ:YHOO) shares are trading higher by $0.08 at $47.64 in Wednesdays session. The catalyst for modest gain is an adjusted Q1 EPS beat of $0.04 along with just shy of $10M beat for revenues.</string>
    <string name="seventh_headline">Yahoo! Inc Turns a Profit Just Before Joining Verizon</string>
    <string name="seventh_story">Data for the first quarter of 2017 in the table above includes changes to Yahoo!s accounting presentation of the Microsoft(NASDAQ:MSFT) search agreement.</string>
    <string name="eighth_headline">Yahoo! Inc. Profit Climbs 112% in Q1</string>
    <string name="eighth_story">(RTTNews.com) - Yahoo! Inc.(YHOO) revealed earnings for its first quarter that advanced from last year. The company said its bottom line climbed to $169.49 million, or $0.18 per share</string>
    <string name="ninth_headline">How Yahoo! Inc. (YHOO) And Its Technical Chart Is Making Things Clearer For ...</string>
    <string name="ninth_story">Yahoo! Inc. (YHOO) has created a compelling message for traders in the most recent trading. That message has grown stronger as the technical chart setup has developed into more composite picture for the stock</string>
    <string name="tenth_headline">Oath Is The New Entity That Will Run Yahoo! Inc. (NASDAQ:YHOO), AOL, Sources Say</string>
    <string name="tenth_story">At this particular moment, Verizon communications Inc(NYSE:VZ) is still making efforts to complete the $4.2 billion acquisitions of Yahoo! Inc(NASDAQ:YHOO) There has been quite high talk in the air in ...</string>
</resources>